<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PATHFIT3</string>


    <string name="title_activity_home_module">homeModule</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_lesson">Lessons</string>
    <string name="title_tutorials">Tutorials</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--Developers Name-->
    <string name="dev_Lorence">Lorence Cerezo</string>
    <string name="dev_Jerard">Jerard Maliwat</string>
    <string name="dev_Jericho">Jericho Mercado</string>
    <string name="dev_Reniel">Reniel John Supan</string>

    <string name="cerezo_gmail">lorence2518cerezo@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="maliwat_gmail">Jerardmaliwat07@gmail.com</string>


    <string name="danceAs">Dance As:</string>


    <!--lesson 1 title-->
    <string name="lesson1_DancePeriods">Dance Periods</string>
    <string name="lesson1_whatIsDance">What is Dance</string>
    <string name="lesson1_PreHistoric">Pre-Historic</string>
    <string name="lesson1_AncientEgypt">Ancient Egypt</string>
    <string name="lesson1_AncientGreek">Ancient Greek</string>
    <string name="lesson1_AncientRome">Ancient Rome</string>
    <string name="lesson1_CatolicChurchInEurope">Catholic Church In Europe</string>
    <string name="lesson1_DarknEarlyMiddleAge">Dark And Early Middle Ages</string>
    <string name="lesson1_EarlyRenaissance">Early Renaissance</string>
    <string name="lesson1_EuropeIn15n16Century">Europe in 15th and 16th Century</string>
    <string name="lesson1_BenefitOfDance">Benefit Of Dance</string>

    <string name="lesson2_natureOfDance">Nature Of Dance</string>


    <string name="DanceTopic">Is the movement of the body in a rhythmic way, usually to music and within given space, for the purpose of expressing and idea or emotion
    , releasing energy, or simply taking delight in movement. \n \nIs an expresssion of the body, following rhythmic patterns and is accompanied by music. From Primitive man expressing emotions
    ins such events such as birth, death marriage, war, among other things, dance has evolved to modern forms of social gatherings. \n \n is one of the oldest and most popular forms of exercise.
    </string>

    <!--prehistoric topic-->
    <string name="prehistoric_Topic">A major form of religious ritual and social expression with primitive cultures. A way of expressing and tribal unity and strength.\n \n An approach for courtship and mating \n \n A means of worship communication and therapeutic experience.</string>


    <!--Ancient egypt-->
    <string name="ancient_egypt_Topic">Become a fullblown and was richly recorded. It is also reflected in wall paintings, reliefs and in literary record in hieroglyphs. \n \n As a medium of religious expression.</string>

    <!--Ancient greek-->

    <string name="ancient_greek_Topic">Is an to military education, And as a form of entertainment display</string>

    <!--Ancient rome-->
    <string name="ancient_rome_Topic">In the Roman era They stopped valuing such qualities in arts as the nations grew wealthy and powerful. The romans ceased to create and perform within the arts themselves.</string>

    <!--Catholic Church-->

    <string name="catolic_church_Topic">The Christian Fathers approved the used of dance, provided that its form and intent were holy and profound. As dances then became part of worships and church activities</string>

    <!--Dark and Early middle ages-->
    <string name="darkMiddleAges_Topic">They performed dance in the village squares to welcome the feudal lords in the castles. \n \n The common people amused themselves by doing dances that were social in character. it is also the beginning of Social Dancing.\n \n
        Two types of dance performed by peasants. \n \n
        Round dance: dancers hold each other by hand forming a long chain and move about in an open closed circle. \n \n
        Couple Dance: It was not as popular than round dance as it was considered scandalous when first seen.
    </string>


    <!-- Renaissance-->
    <string name="renaissance_Topic">Was wholly accepted in courts as a gradual increases of the capitalist class produced patrons of learning and arts in Europe. \n\n Dance and art in general gains impetus \n\n The entertainers now become valuable appendage to the courts of Italy and France.</string>


    <!--Europe in 15th and 16th century-->
    <string name="europe15th_Topic">More court dances performed by nobility came about as well as rise of art in ballet in Italy and France. \n\n Several other dance forms continued to sprout and spread across several countries.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="benefitsOfDance_Physical">Physical</string>
    <string name="benefitsOfDance_PhysicalTopic">Develop cardiovascular endurance\n
    Improves coordination, balance, flexibility and body composition.\n
    Lower risk cardiovascular disease.\m
    Lower body mass index.\n
    Lower resting heart.\n
    Improves lipid metabolism.\n
    Enable joint mobility.\n
    Helps improve and maintain bone density.
    </string>

    <string name="benefitsOfDance_mental_Emotional">Mental/Emotional</string>
    <string name="benefitsOfDance_mental_EmotionalTopic">Help keep the brain sharp.\n
    Decrease incidence of Dementia and Alzheimers Disease.\n
    Decrease depressive symptoms.\n
    Increase self-esteem and improves body image.\n
    Aids in releasing emotional and physical tension.
    </string>

    <string name="benefitsOfDance_Social">Social</string>
    <string name="benefitsOfDance_SocialTopic">Give sense of togetherness within group.\n
    Encourages positive social interaction and interpersonal relationship in group.\n
    Contributes to the individuals for self-actualization in society.\n
    </string>
    <string name="benefitsOfDance_Cultural">Cultural</string>
    <string name="benefitsOfDance_CulturalTopic">Promotes cultural values.</string>


    <string name="traditionalDance_FolknEthnic">Traditional Dances(Folk and Ethnic).</string>
    <string name="traditionalDance_FolknEthnicTopic">Are dances indigenous communities that show cultural traits of people i specific time and place.\n
    Customs and traditions through dance steps and costumes are preserved in traditional dance.
    </string>
    <string name="threeTypesofSocialDances">Three Types of Social Dances.</string>
    <string name="threeTypesofSocialDancesTopic">Ritual Dance.\n


    Life Cycle Dance.\n

    Occupational Dance.\n
    Occupational dance is a form of art that expresses the hardworking value of Filipinos. from different places in the country by showing their local culture and livelihood. The. theme of the folk dance would differ depending on where they live - near the seas, in. the fields, by the mountains, etc.
    </string>

    <string name="traditionalFolkDance">Folk Dance</string>
    <string name="traditionalFolkDanceTopic">According to geographical locations, Folk Dances can be:/n
    National
    Dances with common basic movements, with slight variations.\n\n
    Local/Regional\n
    Dances that are unique to certain localities only.
    </string>
    <string name="traditionalModernContemporary">Modern And Contemporary Dance</string>
    <string name="traditionalModernContemporaryTopic">Modern Dance:
    is the style of dancing where dancers are free to express their feelings through movements.\n\n
    Contemporary Dance:\n
    incorporate the strong legwork and balance off ballet and trunk movements of modern dance.
    </string>
    <string name="cheerDance">CheerDance</string>
    <string name="cheerDanceTopic">A combination of cheering and dancing.\n\n
    Components include the mandatory cheer as well aas number of gymnastics and acrobatic moves such as cartwheels and hand springs
    </string>
    <string name="streetDance">StreetDance</string>
    <string name="streetDanceTopic">HipHop:\n
    is a dance style performed to hip-hop music and usually dance in the street.\n
    it includes a wide range of styles primarily breaking, locking and popping.
    </string>
    <string name="balletDance">Ballet</string>
    <string name="balletDanceTopic">It was taken from  the Italian word "BALLARE" meaning TO DANCE, and "BALLO" referring to DANCES PERFORMED IN BALLROOMS.\n
    combinations of arts of dancing poetry, music, painting.\n
    An artistic, programmatic, scenic dance accompanied by music.
    </string>
    <string name="ballroomDance">Ballroom</string>
    <string name="ballroomDanceTopic">Is a set of partner dances, which are enjoyed both socially and competitively around the world.\n
    because of its performance and entertainment aspects, ballroom dance is also widely enjoyed on stage, film and televisions.
    </string>
    <string name="festivalDance">Festival Dance</string>
    <string name="festivalDanceTopic">Are cultural dances performed to the strong beats of percussion instruments by a community of people sharing the same culture usually done in honor of a patron saint or as a thanksgiving for a bountiful harvest.\n
    Festival Dances may be religious or secular in nature.
    </string>


</resources>